[{"question": "If <code>df</code> is a Pandas dataframe with a column named \"state\", which of these commands will return that column?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "df.loc['state']", "correct": false, "feedback": "<code>df.loc</code> is used to index into the rows. "}, {"code": "df[state]", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The column name must be passes as a string."}, {"code": "df['state']", "correct": true}, {"code": "df('state')", "correct": false, "feedback": "Square brackets are used for indexing, not parentheses"}]}, {"question": "If <code>df</code> is a Pandas dataframe with a columns named \"city\" and \"state\", which of these commands will return a dataframe that contains just those two columns?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "df('city', 'state')", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Remember to use square brackets for indexing into dataframes."}, {"code": "df['city', 'state']", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. You cannot directly pass multiple column names as indexes."}, {"code": "df[ ['city', 'state'] ]", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"code": "df.loc[ ['city', 'state'] ]", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. <code>df.loc</code> is for indexing by rows"}], "answer_cols": 1}, {"question": "If <code>df</code> is a Pandas dataframe with a column named \"state\" what is the effect of the following command?", "code": "df.set_index('state')", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The returned dataframe is now indexed by \"state\". The index of df is unchanged.", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. This command does not change the index of the <code>df</code> dataframe. You can instead change the index of the dataframe stored in <code>df</code> by using the <code>inplace=True</code> keyword argument."}, {"answer": "The index of <code>df</code> is changed to \"state\". There is no returned value.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Try again."}, {"answer": "The index of <code>df</code> is changed to \"state\" and the new dataframe is returned.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Try again."}, {"answer": "Something else.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Try again."}]}, {"question": "If <code>df</code> is a Pandas dataframe with an index that contains the name of the 50 United States,  which of these commands will return the data for Florida?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "df['Florida']", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Using indexing with only square brackets returns columns, each of which contains one variable or feature. We want a row that contains all of the variables or features for Florida."}, {"code": "df.loc['Florida']", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"code": "df.loc('Florida')", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Square brackets are used for indexing."}, {"code": "df.row['Florida']", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. You have the right idea, but \"row\" is not the correct keyword to use to access the rows."}]}, {"question": "If Matplotlib.pyplot has been imported as <code>plt</code>, which of these can be used to specify that the label for the $x$ axis of the current graph should be \"index\"?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "plt.labelx('index')", "correct": false, "feedback": ""}, {"code": "plt.xlabel('index')", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"code": "plt.xtitle('index')", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. There is a <code>plt.title()</code> function, but it is used for setting the title of the plot."}, {"code": "plt['xlabel']='index'", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the label of the $x$-axis is a property of the graph, it cannot be accessed through indexing like this."}], "answer_cols": 1}, {"question": "Which of these Matplotlib functions can be used to add information about which visual indicators (like color or marker) in your plot correspond to which data?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "plt.legend()", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"code": "plt.guide()", "correct": false}, {"code": "plt.add_legend()", "correct": false}, {"code": "plt.add_guide()", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "Which type of plot is better for identifying outliers?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "Histogram", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Histograms do not show all of the data points and so can hide outliers."}, {"code": "Scatter Plot", "correct": true}]}, {"question": "Suppose sets $A$ and $B$ are non-empty subsets of some sample space $S$. If $A$ and $B$ are disjoint, which of the following are true?", "type": "many_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Every element in $S$ is either in $A$ or $B$", "correct": false, "feedback": "No. This is only true if $A$ and $B$ are a partition for $S$."}, {"answer": "$A$ and $B$ have no elements in common", "correct": true}, {"answer": "$A \\cap B = \\emptyset$", "correct": true}, {"answer": "$A \\cup B = \\emptyset$", "correct": false, "feedback": "Since $A$ and $B$ are nonempty, their union will also be nonempty."}]}, {"question": "Which of these is true of a partition of a set $S$?", "type": "many_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Every member of  the set $S$ must be in some subset of the partition.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The partition is a collection of subsets of $S$", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Elements may belong to more than one of the subsets in the partition", "correct": false}, {"answer": "No element in $S$ may belong to more than one of the subsets in the partition", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The union of the subsets in the partition is equal to $S$", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The intersection of the subsets in the partition is equal to $S$", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The intersection of the subsets in the partition is equal to $\\emptyset$ ", "correct": true}]}, {"question": "Which of the following is an example of a partition of the set {1, 2, 3, 4}?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "$\\{1, 2\\}, \\{3\\}, \\{4\\}$", "correct": true}, {"answer": "$\\{1, 2\\}, \\{2, 3\\}, \\{4\\}$", "correct": false, "feedback": "No. The sets $\\{1,2\\}$ and $\\{2,3\\}$ are not disjoint."}, {"answer": "$\\{1\\}, \\{2\\}, \\{3\\}, \\{4\\}$", "correct": true}, {"answer": "$\\{1, 2\\}, \\{4\\}, $", "correct": false, "feedback": "No. None of the sets in the partition contain the element $3$ from $S$, so this is not a partition. "}]}, {"question": "Find the median of the data set $[4, 5, 3, 4, 4]$. ", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 4, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. The sorted data is $[3,4,4,4,5]$, so the middle value is 4."}, {"type": "value", "value": 3, "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although 3 is the middle value of the data as displayed in the question, the median is the middle value of the sorted data."}, {"range": [-100000000, 2.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The median will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"range": [5.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The median will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the mode of the data set $[4, 5, 3, 4, 4]$. ", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 4, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. The value 4 appears 3 times, whereas the other data values only appear 1 time each."}, {"range": [-100000000, 2.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The mode will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"range": [5.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The mode will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the average (sample mean) of the data set $[4, 5, 3, 4, 4]$. ", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 4, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"range": [-100000000, 2.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the mean is not always a value in the data set, it will always be a value that lies between the minimum and maximum data values."}, {"range": [5.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the mean is not always a value in the data set, it will always be a value that lies between the minimum and maximum data values."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the median of the data set $[4, 1, 2, 7, 1]$. ", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 2, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. The sorted data is $[1,1,2,4,7]$, so the middle value is 2."}, {"type": "value", "value": 2, "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although 2 is the middle value of the data as displayed in the question, the median is the middle value of the sorted data."}, {"range": [-100000000, 0.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The median will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"range": [7.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The median will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the mode of the data set $[4, 1, 2, 7, 1]$.", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 1, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. The value 1 appears 2 times, whereas the other data values only appear 1 time each."}, {"range": [-100000000, 0.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The mode will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"range": [7.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The mode will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the average (sample mean) of the data set $[4, 1, 2, 7, 1]$. ", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 3, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"range": [-100000000, 0.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the mean is not always a value in the data set, it will always be a value that lies between the minimum and maximum data values."}, {"range": [7.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the mean is not always a value in the data set, it will always be a value that lies between the minimum and maximum data values."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the median of the data set $[1, 4, 2, 1, 7, 3]$. Since there is an even number of data points, calculate the median as the average of the middle two data points.", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 2.5, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. The sorted data is $[1,1,2,4,7]$, so the middle value is 2."}, {"type": "value", "value": 2, "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although 2 is the middle value of the data as displayed in the question, the median is the middle value of the sorted data."}, {"range": [-100000000, 0.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The median will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"range": [7.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The median will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the mode of the data set $[1, 4, 2, 1, 7, 3]$.", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 1, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. The value 1 appears 2 times, whereas the other data values only appear 1 time each."}, {"range": [-100000000, 0.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The mode will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"range": [7.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The mode will always be a value in the data set, or the average of the middle two values if there are an even number of data points."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "Find the average (sample mean) of the data set $[1, 4, 2, 1, 7, 3]$. ", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 3, "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct."}, {"range": [-100000000, 0.9999], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the mean is not always a value in the data set, it will always be a value that lies between the minimum and maximum data values."}, {"range": [7.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Although the mean is not always a value in the data set, it will always be a value that lies between the minimum and maximum data values."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "What are summary statistics?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Numerical values that summarize a dataset", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Graphical representations of a dataset", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Descriptive words that summarize a dataset", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "What is the sample mean?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The middle value of a dataset", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The most common value in a dataset", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A value that minimizes the mean-squared error to the data", "correct": true}]}, {"question": "What is the median?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "A middle value of a dataset", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The most common value in a dataset", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A value that minimizes the mean-squared error to the data", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "What is the mode?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The middle value of a dataset", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A value that appears the most in a dataset", "correct": true}, {"answer": "A value that minimizes the mean-squared error to the data", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "Which of these summary statistics always has a unique value for a given dataset?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "median", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. When the number of points in a dataset is even, there is not a single data value in the middle of the dataset. In this case, the value of the median can be defined in different ways."}, {"answer": "mode", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. There may be multiple values that all occur the same number of times, and there is no unique mode in such a case."}, {"answer": "mean", "correct": true}]}, {"question": "Which of these statistics is less sensitive to outliers?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "sample mean", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The sample mean can change significantly in the presence of outliers."}, {"answer": "median", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. Because the median returns a value in the middle of the dataset, it is not significantly affected by the particular values of outliers."}]}, {"question": "Given a Pandas dataframe <code>df</code> with a column called 'height', which of these can be used to get a dataframe that contains all the datapoints with height greater than the average within the dataset?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"code": "avg = df.avg()\ndf.query('height > avg')", "correct": false, "feedback": "Pandas Dataframe and Series objects do not have an <code>avg()</code> method. Please try again."}, {"code": "avg = df.mean()\ndf.query('height > avg')", "correct": false, "feedback": "This will compare the values in the 'height' column with the values in the  'avg' column (if it exists) or else throw an error."}, {"code": "avg = df.mean()\ndf.query('height > @avg')", "correct": true}, {"code": "avg = df.mean()\ndf.query('height > $avg')", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. You are correct to recognize that we need to indicate to query that <code>avg</code> is a variable. However, $ is not the correct character for this purpose."}], "answer_cols": 1}, {"question": "Supposed the data used in Section 3.5 is partitioned using the <b>mean</b> of the normalized GDP. How many states have normalized GDP greater than or equal to the average?", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 22, "correct": true}, {"type": "value", "value": 28, "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. You may want to check the direction of your inequality."}, {"type": "value", "value": 25, "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. When we use the median to partition the data, the two groups are of equal size. However, that is not necessarily the case when we use the mean to partition the data."}, {"range": [-100000000, -1e-12], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The number of states satisfying some condition can never be negative."}, {"range": [50.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. There are a total of 50 states, so there cannot be more states than that satisfying any condition."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect."}]}, {"question": "When plotting two histograms on the same axes to compare the results, which of these should generally be used?", "type": "many_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The same bins should be used for each histogram.", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. Using the same bins makes it easier to compare the distributions of values between the two histograms."}, {"answer": "The data should first be partitioned using the median.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The data was partitioned using the median in Section 3.5, but that was not critical the comparing the distributions of values by plotting two histograms on the same axes."}, {"answer": "The <code>alpha</code> parameter should be used to adjust the transparency of the two histograms.", "correct": true, "feedback": "Using transparency makes it easier to see the data when histogram bars overlap."}]}, {"question": "Suppose a histogram for the data $[4,6,2,4,2,4]$ is made using bins with edges at $[1,3,5,7]$. How many value are in the leftmost bin?", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 2, "correct": true}, {"range": [-100000000, -1e-12], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The number of items in a bin cannot be negative."}, {"range": [6.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. There are a total of 6 values in the data set. The number of items in any bin of the histogram cannot be greater than the total number of items."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect. The leftmost bin contains all values in the interval $[1,3)$."}]}, {"question": "Suppose a histogram for the data $[4,6,2,4,2,4]$ is made using bins with edges at $[1,3,5,7]$. How many value are in the center bin?", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 3, "correct": true}, {"range": [-100000000, -1e-12], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The number of items in a bin cannot be negative."}, {"range": [6.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. There are a total of 6 values in the data set. The number of items in any bin of the histogram cannot be greater than the total number of items."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect. The leftmost bin contains all values in the interval $[3,5)$."}]}, {"question": "Suppose a histogram for the data $[4,6,2,4,2,4]$ is made using bins with edges at $[1,3,5,7]$. How many value are in the rightmost bin?", "type": "numeric", "answers": [{"type": "value", "value": 1, "correct": true}, {"range": [-100000000, -1e-12], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The number of items in a bin cannot be negative."}, {"range": [6.000000001, 100000000], "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. There are a total of 6 values in the data set. The number of items in any bin of the histogram cannot be greater than the total number of items."}, {"type": "default", "feedback": "Incorrect. The leftmost bin contains all values in the interval $[5,7]$."}]}, {"question": "What is hypothesis testing?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "A statistical method used to determine whether a hypothesis about a population is likely to be true or not.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "A method used to collect data about a population.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A method used to manipulate data to fit a desired outcome.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A method used to visualize data in a meaningful way.", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "What is the null hypothesis?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The assumption that there is no significant difference between a sample and the population it represents.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The assumption that there is a significant difference between a sample and the population it represents.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The hypothesis that is always rejected.", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "What is the alternative hypothesis?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "An alternative explanation that is disjoint from the null hypothesis.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The assumption that there is no significant difference between a sample and the population it represents.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The hypothesis that is always rejected.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The hypothesis that is always accepted.", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "What is the first step in hypothesis testing?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Formulating a null hypothesis and an alternative hypothesis.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Collecting data.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Calculating a test statistic.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Comparing the test statistic to the critical value.", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "What is a test statistic?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "A single numerical value that is computed from the data that can be used in a statistical test.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The minimum number of data points you must have in your data set.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The maximum number of data points you must have in your data set.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The minimum separate between the means of two data sets for the result to be statistically significant.", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "Which of these are advantages of the model-free approach?", "type": "many_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "It provides exact mathematical formula for probabilities", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Because no model is used, analytical approaches are generally not possible. Thus the results are computed using other techniques, such as resampling (simulation)."}, {"answer": "It does not require the data to be a certain size in order for the model to be accurate", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. Because there is not model, we do not need data to reach a certain size before we can accurately model the data. However, the data may still need to reach a certain size before the results will be accurate."}, {"answer": "It does not rely on mathematical formulas for determining factors such as statistical significance", "correct": true}, {"answer": "It can often be implemented using simulation", "correct": true}]}, {"question": "When is the null hypothesis rejected?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "When the computed $p$-value is less than the specified significance threshold.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "When the computed $p$-value is greater than specified significance threshold.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. In this case, we  would fail to reject the null hypothesis."}, {"answer": "When the test statistic is less than the significance threshold.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. The test statistic is not what is compared to the signficance threshold."}, {"answer": "When a sample value of the test statistic exceeds the observed value of the test statistic.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. When conducting a statistical test via resampling, we may compare the sample value of a test statistic to the observed value, and that affects the computed $p$-value. However, it does not cause the null hypothesis to be rejected directly."}]}, {"question": "When is the null hypothesis accepted?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "When the computed $p$-value is greater than specified significance threshold.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. An NHST is conducted under the assumption that the null hypothesis is true, so we can never accept the null hypothesis. We can only fail to reject it."}, {"answer": "When the computed $p$-value is less than the specified significance threshold.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. In this case, we would <b>reject</b> the null hypothesis."}, {"answer": "When the test statistic is greater than the significance threshold.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. An NHST is conducted under the assumption that the null hypothesis is true, so we can never accept the null hypothesis. We can only fail to reject it."}, {"answer": "When a sample value of the test statistic exceeds the observed value of the test statistic.", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. An NHST is conducted under the assumption that the null hypothesis is true, so we can never accept the null hypothesis. We can only fail to reject it."}]}, {"question": "What is the significance level?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The probability of rejecting the null hypothesis when it is actually true.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The probability of accepting the null hypothesis when it is actually false.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The probability of accepting the alternative hypothesis when it is actually false.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The probability of rejecting the alternative hypothesis when it is actually true.", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "A research wishes to assess the impact of Caribbean ocean surface temperature on the number of hurricanes that form in the North Atlantic Ocean. She partitions the data on the number of hurricanes for each month in the last 100 years based on whether the ocean surface temperature measurement was above or below the median temperature. She then conducts a NHST using the partition data sets. This should be considered:", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "A one-dimensional test", "correct": true, "feedback": " Correct. The NHST is a one-dimensional test that is applied to the data on the number of hurricanes."}, {"answer": "A two-dimensional test", "correct": false, "feedback": "Incorrect. Even though the ocean surface temperature is used to partition the data, the resulting test is one-dimensional. The surface temperature and number of hurricanes are not used together in the statistical test."}, {"answer": "Something else", "correct": false}]}, {"question": "A research wishes to assess the impact of Caribbean ocean surface temperature on the number of hurricanes that form in the North Atlantic Ocean. She tries to find the best line that predicts the number of hurricanes in a month based on the observed ocean surface temperature. This should be considered:", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "A one-dimensional test", "correct": false, "feedback": " Incorrect. Ocean surface temperature and number of hurricanes are used together in finding the best line of fit. This is an example of linear regression."}, {"answer": "A two-dimensional test", "correct": true, "feedback": "Correct. Ocean surface temperature and number of hurricanes are used together in finding the best line of fit. This is an example of linear regression."}, {"answer": "Something else", "correct": false}]}]